Ajay has heard
that Namaskar, welcome to all of you in the news group,
I am Pooja Pratham with you,
I am 12, a grocery
merchant's bag full of Rs 32 lakh was
stolen from ICICI Bank.
A businessman who had come to deposit money in his firm's account in ICICI Bank located at Charmurti intersection in Baran city of Rajasthan, had his
bag full of Rs 32 lakh
stolen from the bank counter. Hemant Goyal, operator of
grocery firm Rajesh Trading Company located in Deendayal Park of the city,
told that in the morning his father Mahavir Goyal had gone to
deposit the firm's seven day's collected payment of Rs 32 lakh in the bank, where he
kept his bank on the counter, there he was about to give a
cheque in the nearby counter, meanwhile the
bag was stolen from the counter. Let me tell you what Himmat Koyal,
proprietor of Rakesh Trading Company has to
say in this regard. He had brought
Bel Patti with Rs 1 lakh for
help from my doctor, the vegetable
got into trouble. The library
takes away the peaceful time on Friday and on Sunday,
Nargarh Bhanwargarh Pragat leading thinker
Quest has brought the matter of my
grocery  Venus's coconut oil in wholesale price
means I have value for feeding all purpose
This incident happened when my father brought the payment from home
He gave me the cannons at the shop for 2 minutes at Deendayal Park
Seeing the danger increasing, he said will Sita and Ravana
come next While leaving, he
kept Ahmed on the counter in the bank and said that this is the
bank for 2 minutes Labbaik This is
from the counter near the check, by the way, a man picks up a bag from him and
takes it away, saying
that today it is the responsibility of the police-administration and all of them, if you have put the
responsibility on the bank people then you will
ask him, at least he is
coming last but friend the guard is sleeping,
what should the employee do,
on getting any information Kotwali police station CI Mangi Lal
Yadav DSP Mahavir Sharma reached the spot
and started searching for the accused by collecting CCTV footage,
some trade union president Lalit
Mohan Khandelwal took the bank employees to task for the theft of money from the bank,
he also
expressed great displeasure for not making security arrangements for the customers coming to the bank, let us tell you
what trade union president Lalit Mohan Khandelwal has to
say in this regard and the speciality was that
we have given the medal to the person of Monday  It is
provided, you can also see from us
that 50 thousand
people of Jindal's family gather there, we
complained to the lead bank officer two weeks ago,
after the officer did the development, we
protested fiercely against this bank, now the square here is
half stolen, after all the bank employee's
bench is responsible for the officers, the
person responsible for the bank officer also came, did
not see in 1 minute, why will you be eaten,
Vinod gave, this means the bank belongs to a
person of Ambedkar age, then
with whom am I sitting, whatever I have taken, this is ours, we are from Seven
Trading Company, it was a
holiday on Thursday, don't get angry, two minutes have passed
but you are with us and if you have
not yet subscribed to our channel, first of all
subscribe to it and do
not forget to press Baba Shravan nearby so that you keep getting
updates of all our interesting and latest news.